Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=The Demon=
=الشيطان=
=Episode 18=
=الحلقة 18=
Master.
يتقن.
What are...
ما هي...
You rogue.
أيها المارق.
Get out!
اخرج!
Master.
يتقن.
You're actually consuming a demon's primordial spirit?
هل أنت في الواقع تستهلك روح الشيطان البدائية؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Are you disobeying me now?
هل تعصيني الآن؟
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
you are no longer my master.
أنت لم تعد سيدي.
What do we do?
ماذا نفعل؟
It's been a month since Her Majesty's return,
لقد مر شهر منذ عودة جلالتها،
but she's been quiet.
لكنها كانت هادئة.
What exactly happened?
ماذا حدث بالضبط؟
I'm worried sick.
أنا قلق للغاية.
Do you think Her Majesty has become
هل تعتقد أن جلالتها أصبحت
a mute?
على كتم الصوت؟
Well,
حسنًا،
you should stop talking nonsense.
ينبغي عليك التوقف عن الكلام الهراء.
If worse comes to worst,
إذا ساءت الأمور،
give Her Majesty a performance.
أعطي جلالتها أداءً.
After all, you're an all-rounder.
بعد كل شيء، أنت شخص متعدد المهارات.
I'm way less than you!
أنا أقل منك بكثير!
With your funny appearance,
مع مظهرك المضحك،
you should give her a performance!
ينبغي عليك أن تقدم لها أداءً!
Enough!
كافٍ!
Now isn't the time
الآن ليس الوقت المناسب
to be joking around.
أن تكون مزاحًا.
I feel depressed
أنا أشعر بالاكتئاب
seeing Her Majesty in that state!
رؤية جلالتها في تلك الحالة!
♪Parasol leaves fall♪
♪أوراق المظلة تتساقط♪
♪A lonely shadow under the moon♪
♪ظل وحيد تحت القمر♪
♪A refreshing evening breeze♪
♪نسيمة مسائية منعشة♪
♪Those whispers♪
♪تلك الهمسات♪
♪Still echo♪
♪لا يزال صدى♪
♪In my heart♪
♪في قلبي♪
♪Dim candle, long windy night♪
♪شمعة خافتة، ليلة طويلة عاصفة♪
♪Floral fragrance fills the garden♪
♪عطر الزهور يملأ الحديقة♪
♪Can't shake it from my mind, it all ends in nothingness♪
♪لا أستطيع التخلص من هذا الأمر في ذهني، كل شيء ينتهي إلى العدم♪
♪Troubling me half my life♪
♪يزعجني نصف حياتي♪
♪You're the sleepless wind chime♪
♪أنت جرس الرياح الذي لا ينام♪
♪Stirring all my thoughts♪
♪إثارة كل أفكاري♪
♪You're the shooting star who lights my loneliness♪
♪أنت النجم الساطع الذي ينير وحدتي♪
♪Spring comes, autumn goes♪
♪يأتي الربيع ويذهب الخريف♪
♪Sun and Moon turn in cycles, that unendurable winter♪
♪تدور الشمس والقمر في دورات، هذا الشتاء الذي لا يطاق♪
♪The unmelting ice♪
♪الجليد الذي لا يذوب♪
♪No matter how far I go, you remain♪
♪مهما ابتعدت، ستبقى♪
♪The scenery I cannot reach♪
♪المناظر الطبيعية التي لا أستطيع الوصول إليها♪
♪You are countless threads, an unbroken dream♪
♪أنت خيوط لا تعد ولا تحصى، حلم غير منقطع♪
♪You are the liquor of sorrow that breaks the heart♪
♪أنت شراب الحزن الذي يكسر القلب♪
♪Drunk yet awake♪
♪سكران ولكن مستيقظ♪
♪Troubling me half my life♪
♪يزعجني نصف حياتي♪
♪You're the sleepless wind chime♪
♪أنت جرس الرياح الذي لا ينام♪
(One month later)
(بعد شهر واحد)
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Chief Fan.
رئيس المشجعين.
I've brought Momo home.
لقد أحضرت مومو إلى المنزل.
Having learned
بعد أن تعلمت
about her identity as a half-demon on that night,
عن هويتها كنصف شيطان في تلك الليلة،
she couldn't accept it.
لم تستطع قبول ذلك.
She then bumped into a demon slayer
ثم اصطدمت بقاتل الشياطين
and put up a tough fight.
وخوض معركة صعبة.
Her true form was revealed after sustaining a heavy injury.
تم الكشف عن شكلها الحقيقي بعد تعرضها لإصابة خطيرة.
Master Shang said
قال السيد شانغ
all 24 types of cooling herbs
جميع أنواع الأعشاب المبردة البالغ عددها 24 نوعًا
are needed
هناك حاجة
to recover her human form.
لاستعادة شكلها البشري.
I tried the herbs I came across along the way,
لقد جربت الأعشاب التي صادفتها على طول الطريق،
but I ended up getting poisoned.
ولكن انتهى بي الأمر بالتسمم.
Luckily, I managed to make it back to Qianchun Mountain.
لحسن الحظ، تمكنت من العودة إلى جبل تشيان تشون.
I hope it's not too late
آمل ألا يكون الوقت متأخرًا جدًا
to save her.
لإنقاذها.
Thank you for all the hard work.
شكرا لكم على كل العمل الشاق.
Ask the Old Turtle to help you get rid of the poison later.
اطلب من السلحفاة العجوز أن تساعدك في التخلص من السم لاحقًا.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
Speak.
يتكلم.
I sneaked into Moyuan City and asked around
تسللت إلى مدينة مويوان وسألت حولها
as you told me.
كما قلت لي.
The people there said
وقال الناس هناك
the consort has been sent
لقد تم إرسال الزوج
to the suburb for recuperation.
إلى الضاحية للتعافي.
They said...
قالوا...
Cut to the chase.
انتقل مباشرة إلى صلب الموضوع.
The consort has been in a coma,
لقد كان الزوج في غيبوبة،
and his days are numbered.
وأيامه معدودة.
It's the demon core.
إنه جوهر الشيطان.
Shen Wangchen!
شين وانغشن!
(How could it be?)
(كيف يمكن أن يكون ذلك؟)
She's fallen for it, and she won't be able to move for now.
لقد وقعت في الفخ، ولن تكون قادرة على التحرك الآن.
Hurry and catch her.
اسرع وأمسكها.
Mr. Zhen?
السيد تشن؟
Zhen Gui.
تشن غوي.
I heard there's been some evil demon
سمعت أن هناك بعض الشياطين الشريرة
in the city again.
في المدينة مرة أخرى.
Find out that demon's whereabouts immediately.
اكتشف مكان وجود هذا الشيطان على الفور.
Well, Young Madam,
حسنًا، سيدتي الشابة،
just what's the matter
ما الأمر بالضبط
with Young City Lord?
مع سيد المدينة الشاب؟
You must hang in there.
يجب عليك الصمود.
You have our support,
لديك دعمنا
so don't ever give up.
لذلك لا تستسلم أبدًا.
Why?
لماذا؟
Shen Wangchen and his family
شين وانغتشين وعائلته
have been treating you well.
لقد تم التعامل معك بشكل جيد.
They're treating me well?
هل يعاملونني بشكل جيد؟
I have
أملك
dedicated half of my life
كرس نصف حياتي
to Moyuan City.
إلى مدينة مويوان.
But what have I received in return?
ولكن ماذا حصلت في المقابل؟
All the glory
كل المجد
belongs to the Shen family!
تنتمي إلى عائلة شين!
The City Lord had been muddle-headed and sheltering his people.
لقد كان سيد المدينة مرتبكًا ويحمي شعبه.
Before his departure,
قبل رحيله،
he still insisted on making
لا يزال يصر على صنع
his badly sick son
ابنه المريض بشدة
the next City Lord.
سيد المدينة القادم.
That is unfair to me!
هذا غير عادل بالنسبة لي!
The Shen family is nothing but incompetent.
عائلة شين ليست سوى غير كفؤة.
I should be
ينبغي لي أن أكون
the City Lord instead!
سيد المدينة بدلا من ذلك!
Now that
الآن بعد ذلك
Shen Wangchen is gone,
لقد رحل شين وانغتشين
I'm blessed enough
أنا محظوظ بما فيه الكفاية
to have the goods on them.
أن يكون لديهم البضاعة.
Tonight,
الليلة،
I shall eradicate the Shen family
سأقضي على عائلة شين
after dealing with you.
بعد التعامل معك.
Shen Wangchen.
شين وانغشن.
Evil demon.
شيطان شرير.
You will meet your demise today.
سوف تقابل مصيرك اليوم.
Do it!
افعلها!
♪Where did I lose my direction?♪
♪أين فقدت اتجاهي؟♪
♪Only emptiness is left♪
♪لم يبق سوى الفراغ♪
♪Restless, sleepless, we part ways♪
♪أرق، بلا نوم، افترقنا♪
♪As sorrow slowly grows within♪
♪كما ينمو الحزن ببطء في الداخل♪
♪Tears can't heal, smiles still ache♪
♪الدموع لا يمكن أن تشفى، والابتسامات لا تزال تؤلم♪
♪Because my heart's with you♪
♪لأن قلبي معك♪
♪Your gaze melted the haze♪
♪نظرتك أذابت الضباب♪
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
♪انتظر عودتك لفترة طويلة♪
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
♪تذكّرني الشمس الغاربة بك♪
♪If the clear sky is torn by storm and rain one day♪
♪إذا تمزقت السماء الصافية بالعاصفة والمطر يومًا ما♪
♪Tears will flow♪
♪الدموع سوف تتدفق♪
♪I will still wait here with no regrets♪
♪سوف أظل أنتظر هنا دون أي ندم♪
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
♪انتظر عودتك لفترة طويلة♪
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
♪تذكّرني الشمس الغاربة بك♪
♪In the amber desert, you turn away with tears in your eyes♪
♪في الصحراء الكهرمانية، تبتعد والدموع في عينيك♪
♪I'll welcome you back in a red dress♪
♪سأرحب بك مرة أخرى في ثوب أحمر♪
♪Waiting forever with no regrets♪
♪الانتظار إلى الأبد دون أي ندم♪